Hello, Legends.In this video, we'll be diving into the new Cloud Opus 4.6, and we'll be explicitly exploring the new Agent Teams.So I'm going to be running an experiment in this video where I'm going to be spooling up a Cloud Code instance using the Opus 4.6 model, getting one agent to build out a certain project for us.And then I'm going to be spooling up another Cloud Code instance, enabling the Agent Teams mode, then giving the exact same prompt, and then comparing the results.
哈囉各位。在這支影片中，我們要來深入了解全新的 Claude Opus 4.6，特別是來探索全新的 Agent Teams。我在這支影片中要做一個實驗：我會先啟動一個 Claude Code 實例，使用 Opus 4.6 模型，讓一個代理幫我們建構一個特定的專案。接著我會再啟動另一個 Claude Code 實例，開啟 Agent Teams 模式，給它完全相同的提示詞，然後比較兩者的結果。
So I wanna quickly touch on the anatomy of an agent team versus what we previously had, which was a sub-agent.So sub-agents work by receiving a very specific prompt, then that prompt is actioned and completed, and then only the results of the completion are shared back with the main context window.Whereas agent teams are a little bit more sophisticated.
我想先快速講一下 Agent Teams 的架構，以及它跟我們之前用的子代理有什麼不同。子代理的運作方式是接收一個非常具體的提示詞，然後執行並完成該任務，最後只把完成的結果回傳給主要的上下文視窗。而 Agent Teams 則複雜精密許多。
So when we enable the agent team, we actually first pull up a team lead that manages a number of different prompts, depending what kind of tasks we need to complete, the team leader will then distribute those prompts amongst very specialized teammates,And all of these teammates actually spool up their own instance of Claude code.So this is important to note because sub-agents actually work within the one instance or the one session, but then each of these guys actually runs in their own isolated and dedicated session.So the sub-agent, there is...
當我們啟用 Agent Teams 時，系統會先拉起一個 Team Lead 來管理一系列不同的提示詞。根據我們需要完成什麼類型的任務，Team Lead 會將這些提示詞分配給各個專精的隊友。而且每個隊友都會啟動自己的 Claude Code 實例。這一點很重要，因為子代理其實是在同一個實例或同一個工作階段中運作，但這些隊友每個人都在自己獨立且專屬的工作階段中執行。所以子代理的話...
lower token consumption and technically speaking, a lower quality of output.They're meant to be used for like simpler tasks.But when you're using an agent team, because they have their own instance, they can actually use a lot more tokens and they can run more independently.Now the interesting thing is that all these guys can actually speak between each other.So if teammate A is working on the front end, teammate B is working on the back end, if teammate A gets stuck, they can directly communicate with teammate B to kind of get unstuck or to try and figure things out.
token 消耗量比較低，理論上輸出品質也比較低。它們比較適合用來處理較簡單的任務。但當你使用 Agent Teams 時，因為每個隊友都有自己的實例，它們可以使用更多的 token，也能更獨立地運作。有趣的是，所有隊友之間其實可以互相溝通。所以如果隊友 A 在做前端、隊友 B 在做後端，當隊友 A 卡住時，可以直接跟隊友 B 溝通來解決問題或一起想辦法。
And they can keep communicating back andbetween the team lead and then the teammate.Whereas in this instance, you'd pull up the sub-agent that would complete the task and then communicate it back.And if they had to do another run at completing a specific part of work, it wouldn't actually be a direct communication.It would just kind of be very transactional in nature.And then the final interesting thing is that we can actually speak to any one of the team members at any time.
而且它們可以在 Team Lead 和隊友之間持續來回溝通。相比之下，子代理的模式是完成任務後把結果回傳。如果需要再做一輪修改，那也不算是直接溝通，本質上就只是很事務性的互動。最後一個有趣的地方是，我們其實可以隨時跟任何一位團隊成員直接對話。
So when we're in the Claude Code terminal, we'll see later on that we actually have access to toggle between the team leader and any of the open teammates and just communicate with them directly so we can change their scope of work, getfeedback on what they're working on, and even try and unblock them if they get stuck.Anthropic summarizes the difference really well over here, where they say sub-agents are better at working at smaller, more focused tasks, and then agent teams are better at figuring out complex problems where they can collaborate together.
在 Claude Code 終端機裡，我們稍後會看到可以在 Team Lead 和任何開啟中的隊友之間切換，直接跟它們溝通。這樣我們可以調整它們的工作範圍、取得工作進度回饋，甚至在它們卡住的時候幫忙解決問題。Anthropic 在這裡把差異總結得非常好：子代理比較適合處理較小、較專注的任務，而 Agent Teams 比較適合解決需要協作的複雜問題。
So here's a really good example of when you would actually fire off an agent team.So if you want to review a code base, typically when you just issue one agent that task, they'll latch onto one theme or one key area, and then struggle to actually diversify their approachWhereas if you have an agent team, you can give each of those members in a team a different distinct area to focus on.Therefore, each of these areas will get an appropriate coverage from each agent.
這裡有一個很好的例子，說明什麼時候該啟動 Agent Teams。如果你想審查一個程式碼庫，通常一個代理會抓住一個主題或一個關鍵區域，然後很難多元化它的審查方式。但如果你有 Agent Teams，你可以讓團隊中每個成員專注在不同的明確領域上。這樣每個領域都能得到各個代理適當的覆蓋。
And the second example from Anthropic is in a very similar light, where if you want to understand a complex issue, typically one agent will again just find one possible explanation, one key theme, latch onto it.So then you actually want to prompt up an agent team and then give different members of the team distinct areas to explore and to look at.So I've got two instances of cursor open up.I've got a normal instance where I'll just be using one agent to build out this prompt for us.
Anthropic 的第二個例子也是類似的情況：如果你想了解一個複雜的問題，通常一個代理只會找到一種可能的解釋、一個關鍵主題，然後就緊抓不放。所以你應該啟動一個 Agent Teams，讓團隊中不同的成員去探索和研究不同的方向。我已經開了兩個 Cursor 實例。一個是一般的實例，只用一個代理來幫我們建構這個提示詞對應的專案。
And then another instance where I'll be spooling up an agent team and giving it the exact same prompt.So I'm just spooling up the very first instance using this single agent.I'm asking it to build me a very basic task manager app as a single page web application.So it's nothing fancy.It's just enough for us to test this out and see what happens.So now in our next terminal, in order for us to set this up, we first have to initialize agent teams.
然後另一個實例會啟動 Agent Teams，給它完全相同的提示詞。我先開第一個實例，使用單一代理。我請它幫我建構一個非常基本的任務管理應用程式，做為單頁式網頁應用。不需要太花俏，夠我們測試並看看結果就好。現在在下一個終端機裡，要設定 Agent Teams，我們首先要初始化它。
So to enable agent teams, we have to go into our settings.json file and then add this environment variable, which is Claude Code Experimental, and then toggle it to equal 1.So just before we do that, make sure that you're running the latest version of Claude Code.And you can just check which models you have available to you by going into /model.And once you get into here, you've got two different options for an Opus 4.6 model.You have the regular Opus 4.6.
要啟用 Agent Teams，我們需要進入 settings.json 檔案，然後加入環境變數 Claude Code Experimental，設定為 1。在做這件事之前，先確認你的 Claude Code 是最新版本。你可以輸入 /model 來查看有哪些可用的模型。進去之後你會看到 Opus 4.6 模型有兩個選項。一個是一般的 Opus 4.6。
Then you also have the 1 million token context 4.6, which is better for those longer sessions and more complex tasks.If you toggle with your keyboard left and right, you also see that on the very bottom, you can toggle your reasoning effort.So you go low effort, mid effort, and then high effort, where high effort basically uses unrestricted amount of tokens, which will give you better results for more complex tasks and bigger project builds.I'm gonna leave mine on low effort and just gonna use the regular Opus 4.6 model.
另一個是 100 萬 token 上下文的 4.6 版本，比較適合較長的工作階段和更複雜的任務。如果你用鍵盤左右切換，還會在最底部看到可以調整推理強度，分成低、中、高三個等級。高推理強度基本上會使用不受限的 token 量，對更複雜的任務和較大型的專案建構會有更好的結果。我這次把推理強度留在低，然後使用一般的 Opus 4.6 模型。
And I'm gonna ask Claude Code to initialize the, basically change the settings for me so we can initialize agent teams.So Claude's found that file.Let's just give it permissions for this session.And it's identified the change that it has to make.So it's going to be adding exactly what we had in the instructions.So I'm going to go yes once again.And done.Looks like Claude code has made that change for us in the settings.json file.Now, important to note, we cannot start an agent team in this specific session.We have to restart Claude code.
我要請 Claude Code 幫我初始化，基本上就是改設定來啟用 Agent Teams。Claude 找到那個檔案了。我們給它這次工作階段的權限。它已經辨識出需要做的變更，就是加入我們說明裡的那個設定。我按確認，完成了。看起來 Claude Code 已經在 settings.json 裡做好變更了。重要的是，我們不能在這個工作階段中啟動 Agent Teams，必須重新啟動 Claude Code。
So to do that, you can just go into plus and then go into a new terminal.restart ClaudeCode here, and now Claude will be able to access the agent teams.So it's important to know when we want to initialize a new agent team at the prompt level, we have to explicitly give those instructions to ClaudeCode.We have to say, create an agent team to XYZ to complete some kind of task or project for us.And here is our prompt.So create an agent team to build out the following for us.
要重新啟動的話，點加號然後開一個新的終端機。在這裡重新啟動 Claude Code，現在 Claude 就能使用 Agent Teams 了。重要的是，當我們想在提示詞層級初始化一個新的 Agent Teams 時，必須明確地給 Claude Code 這些指令。我們需要說「create an agent team」來完成某個任務或專案。這就是我們的提示詞：建立一個 Agent Teams 來幫我們建構以下內容。
And this is the exact same prompt that we gave to the very first instance on Cursor, where we had just the single agent working on this project.So here we are, ClaudeCode is immediatelytelling us I'll create a team to build out this task manager app in parallel.Let me set up the team and then break down the work.So first we're building out the plan of what we need built and then we'll be assigning each of those items from the plan to a separate agent on our team.
這和我們給 Cursor 上第一個實例的提示詞完全一樣，那個是只有單一代理在做這個專案的。好，Claude Code 立刻告訴我們：我會建立一個團隊來平行建構這個任務管理應用程式，讓我先設定團隊然後分解工作。首先我們要建構出需要做什麼的計畫，然後把計畫中的每個項目分配給團隊中的各個代理。
So now we're supporting up the teammates for each task that we created.So the first task is to create the HTML and CSS.So the UI builder is going to be working on the HTML and CSS.Once that's done, I'll spawn up the JS developer to add the application logic.Let me wait for the first task to complete.So after each task was definedthen Claude Code was able to spin up the teammates.So it's found the very first teammate, which is building out the looks like the front end, the HTML and CSS.
現在我們正在為每個任務啟動隊友。第一個任務是建立 HTML 和 CSS，所以 UI 建構者會負責 HTML 和 CSS。完成之後，我會啟動 JS 開發者來加入應用程式邏輯。讓我等第一個任務完成。每個任務定義好之後，Claude Code 就能啟動隊友了。它找到了第一個隊友，看起來是在建構前端的 HTML 和 CSS。
And then on the bottom over here, we can see that there's two teammate agents already deployed.We have the main agent, which is the person that's the actual team lead, and then we have the UI builder agent.And if I hold shift and I press up and down arrows, I can see that I have access to the team lead to speak with them directly.And if I press shift and then down, I have the UI builder.Now in this instance, the app is pretty simple, but I've actually built outa couple of apps where there's three agents working in parallel.
在底部我們可以看到已經部署了兩個隊友代理。我們有主要的代理，也就是 Team Lead，然後有 UI 建構者代理。如果我按住 Shift 加上下方向鍵，可以看到我能跟 Team Lead 直接對話。按 Shift 加下，就會到 UI 建構者。在這個例子中應用程式比較簡單，但我其實有建構過幾個有三個代理平行運作的應用程式。
And we just click yes for these edits.And then I actually have options of three different agents that I can speak with at one time.And sometimes during the course of the project, you'll actually find that once one specific component is finished and the feedback goes back to the team lead, the team lead will create some new project and actually spin up new agents to work on the next part of the build.So it gets pretty advanced and it's also really fun to see.There we go.So we're actually spinning up different agents now.
我們對這些編輯按確認就好。然後我其實可以同時跟三個不同的代理對話。有時候在專案進行中，你會發現當某個特定元件完成後，回饋傳回 Team Lead，Team Lead 就會建立新任務，並啟動新的代理來處理建構的下一個部分。這變得非常進階，看起來也很有趣。好了，我們現在正在啟動不同的代理。
So task one assigned to the UI builder, build the HTMLstructure and CSS theming create the foundational HTML structure.We've got a skeleton given to it and actually a very clear set of instructions for this builder.And now we can see then below if I hold down shift and I toggle up and down we've got the team lead just as before then we have the JavaScript dev which is the new agent that was just rated and then we have the UI builder.
任務一分配給 UI 建構者：建立 HTML 結構和 CSS 主題，建構基礎的 HTML 結構。我們給了它一個骨架，而且有一套非常清楚的指令。現在在下方，如果我按住 Shift 上下切換，我們有跟之前一樣的 Team Lead，然後有 JavaScript 開發者——這是剛建立的新代理，還有 UI 建構者。
Coming back to our first agent let's just click accept on these permissions and there we go it's actually just finished.Now let's pull this up.Okay so this looks really cool.We haveViews on our side, due date, priority, projects.We also have toggle for night mode and day mode.Let's create a new task.So cook, dinner, I'll leave the description empty.We pop up a little calendar.That's awesome.Subtasks, even subtasks, that's cool.
回到我們的第一個代理，點接受這些權限，好了，它其實已經完成了。讓我們看看成果。好，這看起來真的很酷。我們側邊有檢視方式、到期日、優先順序、專案，還有夜間模式和日間模式的切換。來建立一個新任務。煮晚餐，描述先留空。彈出了一個小日曆，太棒了。子任務，居然有子任務，太酷了。
So buy food, let's hit enter.
買食材，按 Enter。
All right, just click new subtask, cook food, and then a new one, eat food.So that's interesting.It's like a layered, it's like a folder.It's like a layered task.Typically, like from demo task managers that I've built, it's usually one top layer and then you just click close in a top layer, but now you have little subtasks, which is what a lot of actual like ClickUp, like actual task managers do.They'll have subtasks within a task.So that's really interesting.We have active task completed.
好，點新增子任務，煮食物，再一個，吃食物。這很有趣，就像分層的，像資料夾一樣，是有層級的任務。通常我以前做的範例任務管理器只有一個頂層，你點一下就關閉。但現在有了子任務，這就是像 ClickUp 這些真正的任務管理工具會做的事，在任務裡面還有子任務。非常有趣。我們有進行中的任務和已完成的。
So if I actually just click one, two, and if I click this cook dinner,And it goes into the completed view.That's nice.And let me just see if I right click on here.Okay, we have edit, reopen.Now this functionality is actually insane.I actually can't believe that.I can change priority by doing the right click on here.Move to inbox, move to work, move to personal.Okay, so we have different views over here.So personal view shows that project.Let's move it across to inbox now.
如果我點這些勾選，然後點煮晚餐，它就移到已完成的檢視裡了。不錯。讓我右鍵點這裡看看。好的，有編輯、重新開啟。這個功能真的太強了，我完全不敢相信。我可以透過右鍵來更改優先順序。移到收件匣、移到工作、移到個人。好，我們這邊有不同的檢視。個人檢視顯示那個專案。現在把它移到收件匣。
And it moves.This is beautiful.This is really nice.This is Opus 4.6 on its own, and that is very impressive.And if we delete that, then let's go to create a new project as well.I'm gonna call this dinner.Let's click enter.There we go.So as this stands, this is actually very impressive.It looks really good.It doesn't look like it's been made by a botch AI, like a lot of the older apps that we'd be building across the last few months.And on top of that, this is usable.It's immediately usable.
移過去了。太漂亮了，真的很棒。這是 Opus 4.6 單獨完成的，非常令人印象深刻。把它刪掉之後，再來建立一個新專案。我叫它晚餐，按 Enter。好了。就目前而言，這真的非常令人印象深刻。看起來很好，不像是那種粗糙的 AI 做出來的，不像我們過去幾個月建構的那些舊應用程式。而且最重要的是，這是可以直接使用的，馬上就能用。
The functionality is very easy, very smooth to use.And it gave us a bunch of different sections, due dates, priorities, and projects as a starting point.This is fantastic.You could literally use this to run your personal life without buying another tool.So now back in the agent team, we see there was a shutdown request because all the tasks were completed.Let's fire this up and see how it looks.Okay, so this looks really interesting.The first thing I want to note is that the name was the exact same as that first version from the single agent task flow.
功能非常簡單、操作非常順暢。它給了我們一堆不同的分類：到期日、優先順序和專案作為起點。太棒了，你真的可以用這個來管理個人生活，不用再買其他工具。現在回到 Agent Teams 這邊，我們看到有一個關閉請求，因為所有任務都完成了。讓我們打開來看看。好，這看起來很有趣。我第一個注意到的是名稱跟單一代理版本完全一樣。
Otherwise, this looks a lot more polished.We have the night mode and day mode with a bit more of a transition between both.Let's add a task here when it's to be done.Cook dinner, leave a description for now.We can choose the date.So it looks like the date creation function or the task creation functionality is very similar.Now we've got subtasks here as well.So buy food, add a new one, cooked food, and if I hit enter, okay, just creates the task, nice.
除此之外，這看起來精緻多了。我們有夜間模式和日間模式，切換的過渡效果更好。來加一個任務，煮晚餐，描述先不填。可以選擇日期。看起來建立任務的功能非常相似。這裡也有子任務。買食材，再加一個，煮食物，按 Enter，好，任務就建立了，不錯。
So let's actually go back to edit this and have one more eat food.We can't forget about eating the food.Save the task.If I click on write.Okay, so our options here are a little bit different.We can edit the task, duplicate or move it to a different section and we can just choose numbers here.So that navigation panel is a little bit different.If I just come back into here and quickly create an eat food task.
回去編輯這個，再多加一個吃食物。我們不能忘記吃東西嘛。儲存任務。如果我點右鍵。好，這裡的選項有點不一樣。我們可以編輯任務、複製、或移到不同的分類，可以直接選數字。所以導覽面板有點不同。讓我回到這裡快速建立一個吃食物的任務。
and I create this, if I do the right-click here, I've got a lot more of a navigation panel.It looks a little bit less polished, less refined, but it is, in my opinion for me, a bit more usable, because I just like having everything easy access here.But you can definitely see this side panel over here, it does look a lot more polished, so I'm just going to quickly flip across for both.This is that single agent one.We're using more of these emojis.
建好了。如果我右鍵點擊，有更多的導覽選項。看起來沒那麼精緻、沒那麼細緻，但以我個人的使用習慣來說其實更好用，因為我喜歡所有東西都能方便存取。不過你可以看到這個側邊面板確實精緻多了。讓我快速切換兩個版本來比較。這是單一代理的版本，用了更多表情符號。
We could definitely go back and refine this and say don't use the emojis, but I do like how it's more filled out over here.But then the agent team one does look a lot more refined.So I actually like the side panel here.It's very nice.We didn't have the settings panel in the first version, but if I click this, it doesn't actually go anywhere.And if I go onto board view, it doesn't go anywhere as well.So I'm just going to come back to the agent team.I'm going to click escape to return to the team lead.
我們當然可以回去修改說不要用表情符號，但我喜歡這個版本填得比較豐富。不過 Agent Teams 的版本確實精緻多了。我很喜歡這裡的側邊面板，很好看。第一個版本沒有設定面板，但我點這個按鈕卻沒有反應。看板檢視也沒有反應。所以我回到 Agent Teams 這邊，按 Escape 回到 Team Lead。
I'm just going to say, can you confirm the JavaScript is working because some of the buttons, which was settings or board view, they don't work.So let's see what happens when we try and fix this.So there we go, looks like we have a fix.Now the board view and the settings buttons will actually do something.So now coming back to our task manager, if I click on board view, nice, actually looks like we can drag and drop between here as well.
我跟它說：你能確認 JavaScript 有正常運作嗎？因為有些按鈕像是設定和看板檢視不會動。來看看修復的結果。好，看起來修好了。現在看板檢視和設定按鈕實際上有功能了。回到我們的任務管理器，點看板檢視，不錯，看起來我們還可以在不同欄位之間拖放。
So the board view now works and it changes the status as we drag it to a different section of our pipeline between urgent to high to medium.It actually applies that to the task as well.And now let's check out the settings panel.So over here we have light mode or dark mode.Okay, default view and then we have export data as JSON or import and then clear all data.So now to do a postmortem between both builds, eitherusing the single agent or the team of agents.
看板檢視現在可以用了，當我們把任務拖到流水線的不同區塊時，從緊急到高到中，狀態也會跟著改變，它也會相應地套用到任務上。現在來看看設定面板。這裡有亮色模式或暗色模式、預設檢視，然後有匯出資料為 JSON 或匯入，還有清除所有資料。現在來做兩個版本的事後比較分析，一個用單一代理，一個用 Agent Teams。
The single agent took six minutes and 55 seconds to build out the task manager.And I actually like how this looks more than the agent team app.I like that they're using emojis over here.It's a bit more fun.It makes me want to create tasks and follow through with them.And then looking at the agent team, the first part of the build was actually a little bit faster.So it was four minutes and 50 seconds versus six minutes and 50 seconds.So two minutes faster.But then we had to come back and rework the Kanban board button and also the settings button.
單一代理花了六分五十五秒來建構任務管理器。而且我其實比較喜歡這個版本的外觀，勝過 Agent Teams 的應用程式。我喜歡這邊用了表情符號，比較有趣味性，讓我想去建立任務並完成它們。再看 Agent Teams 的版本，建構的第一階段其實快一點：四分五十秒對比六分五十秒，快了兩分鐘。但我們後來必須回去修復看板檢視按鈕和設定按鈕。
And that added an additional 1.5 minutes to our build time.So I would say the build time is like for like.And in this portal, while I don't necessarily like the UI as much as the first one, I could definitely fix it by prompting up.I do like that it went a little bit deeper and it had the board view and I do like the settings panel.So I didn't even prompt up that I wanted a settings panel.I didn't even think of having an export or an import functionality to take tasks between workspaces.
那又多花了一分半鐘的建構時間。所以我認為兩者的建構時間算是差不多。在 Agent Teams 這個版本中，雖然我不一定那麼喜歡它的介面，但可以透過調整提示詞來修正。我喜歡它做得更深入，有看板檢視，我也喜歡設定面板。我甚至沒有在提示詞中提到想要設定面板，也沒想到要有匯出匯入功能來在不同工作空間之間轉移任務。
So I've been testing the new Cloud Opus 4.6 model on some other projects that I've been building.I ended up building a car dealership portal that runs tasks.It has a database on Supabase.I installed the Supabase MCP into the 4.6 model and was able to integrate a database for authentication and start building a bit of the backend so it can actually create customers, create tasks and jobs and all this stuff.So that was very interesting.If you guys want to see more of an advanced build, please let me know in the comments.
我也一直在其他專案上測試新的 Claude Opus 4.6 模型。我建了一個汽車經銷商管理入口來執行任務，它有一個 Supabase 的資料庫。我把 Supabase MCP 安裝到 4.6 模型中，就能整合資料庫做身份驗證，並開始建構部分後端功能，讓它可以建立客戶、建立任務和工單之類的東西。非常有趣。如果你們想看更進階的建構，請在留言區告訴我。
Thanks for watching and I'll see in the next one.
感謝收看，我們下支影片見。